Hey! You got oshiruko all over me!
That stuff ain't fit to eat!
Might as well cover yourself in it!
Bring out more soup!
Let's have a food fight!
Spill it all!
Why?!
What the hell's wrong with you idiots?!
Why do you get all this food?!
What's he doing?!
Is red bean soup that good?!
Yeah, it's delicious.
Nothing else even comes close.
So how come...
you guys get to waste it
while Tama goes hungry?!
Gum-Gum...
Elephant Gun!
Captain, look!
It's Straw Hat!
What does that moron think he's doing?!
We disguised ourselves to sneak
through the banquet hall...
Oh, well...
Kid?
Leave him!
While they're focused on
that idiot, we'll slip right by.
What the...?!
Seriously...
You just had to cause a scene!
I made a beeline for the source...
but you've already ruined everything!
Why the hell can't you just sneak in quietly?!
Really?
Does he hear himself right now?
These jerks had it coming!
They were dumping oshiruko for fun!
Oshiruko?!
This soup is so delicious!
In that case, I'll cut them to ribbons!
What kind of surprise is this?
Oshiruko?
Why would that set them off?
Those guys are hopeless.
I can't work with them.
Man, we really stepped in it.
But it's not time to start the battle yet.
I know, but they haven't
figured out who we are yet.
So... Happy now?
Yeah!
Then...
let's beat it!
Okay!
They're making a run for it!
Catch them!
Hey, now...
What's with all the commotion?
Don't tell me...
Are they...?
A-pow-pow! Yo, check it out!
Yo, Queen! I got the scoop
of the century! It'll blow you away!
So listen up, okay?!
Okay, Apoo!
Apoo! Apoo!
Don't be an ass! Share the news with the class!
Brother Apoo! Gimme a nice rhyme, 'poo!
That voice...
Check it out!
Udon's labor camps? That's your domain!
Trying to break out? It'll be in vain!
Once you're inside, you're trapped like a rat!
But check out those two!
What's up with that?!
Oh, should we fight?
Now that I look closely at that duo raising hell,
those jailbreakers down
there are ringing a bell!
No way!
Yes way! You ain't trippin', yo!
It's Straw Hat Luffy and Pirate Hunter Zoro!
So he broke out of the prison...
This is Warden Babanuki in Udon.
So, all is well.
Tonight, we're celebrating the Golden Festival!
So catch them as a gift for me!
Hey, Queen!
What's the prize for bringing them to you?
Well, it just so happens
there's someone I want to axe...
from the Soaring Six!
Whoever catches these rats
for me can have the vacant spot!
The Soaring Six, huh?
Now that's my kind of reward!
That spot is as good as mine!
Apoo!
That must be Kaido's castle back there!
Let's clear a path and get inside!
Sure!
These guys seem like a real pain!
What's their deal?
They must be the ones that ate SMILE fruits!
Check out my battle music!
Scratch!
Bop!
Luffy!
What the...?! Something punched me?!
That guy was in an alliance with Jaggy's crew...
Slash!
Zoro!
I got cut?!
But he doesn't have a blade!
I didn't see an attack either...!
What kind of ability does he have?
Boom!
Luffy!
Ch-Ch-Ch-Ch... Check it out!
Whoa, whoa, gimme a break!
That was too easy!
It's no use! We gotta get out of here!
Hey, you guys!
Don't let them get away!
If you want that spot in
the Soaring Six, you gotta work for it!
If we take a bad beating here...
we won't be able to knock out Kaido!
As expected, it's not just their numbers.
They're pretty tough!
Soaring Six, here I come!
Sorry.
I'm all good now.
Of course you are.
Guess these disguises are kinda pointless now.
You're right.
It's hard to fight in them, too.
Alright!
We're done hiding! Let's
hurry up and break through!
Right!
It's no use.
You guys are in my range.
Check it out!
What can we do?
Scratch!
Don't do it, Kid!
You'll blow our cover, too!
I don't give a damn!
That double-crossing son of a bitch...!
Everything is all his fault!
Go to hell, Apoo!
Kid!
Punk...
Gibson!
Oh, Jaggy!
That dummy!
Apoo!
Hey, that guy's an impostor!
What?!
Don't tell me...!
Is that...?!
It's Captain Kid!
What the hell is Kid doing here?
He's supposed to be locked up in Udon, too!
You better have a damn good
explanation for this, Babanuki!
You were so eager to form an alliance...
Back then...
I should've put it together!
You were already one of Kaido's informants!
Kaido knew every move that we made...
because you were reporting to him, right?!
You're just a kid after all!
What?!
Did you think our alliance was strong enough
to take down one of the Four Emperors?!
Get real!
After all, when have you ever heard...
of a pirate alliance having a happy ending?!
Scratch!
Slash!
I thought you were dead...
Well, Kid?
You scum!
Queen!
They're running wild!
How are we supposed
to catch them alive like this?!
Who said you couldn't kill 'em?
Repel!
Anyone with a death wish, step right up!
I'll be your executioner!
There he is!
I knew Killer would be here too!
Kid! Let's get out of here!
There's nothing to gain
from fighting them here!
I guess you've got a point...
Hey, stop!
Even if you kill them,
you can't be part of the Soaring Six!
Whoa, whoa, quit it!
You'll hurt us, too!
Get out of here!
Somebody, stop him!
I guess that's my cue...
Time to scram!
Seems like they can't control
that guy! But who is he?!
A giant? No, he's way too big!
Attaboy, Haccha!
Looks like I'll be taking Kid's head!
Jaggy! Let's make a dash for the castle!
Man...
I knew you'd start something, Jaggy!
Look who's talking, Luffy!
You're just as bad, Roronoa!
They're all hopeless.
Yay!
Once I break out my battle
music, there's no escape!
Here we go!
Encore! Check it out!
Hey! Cover your ears!
Check it out!
Boom!
Listen up, guys!
Apoo attacks using sound itself!
If you can hear the attack,
it's already too late to dodge!
So keep an eye on him!
– What?
Since it's so important,
I'll say it one more time!
Okay!
They finally contacted me!
They said the ship was fine,
so they should be here soon!
How curious...
Are you sure, Big Mom?
There's been no word of new
arrivals from Mogura Port...
Port?
There's a port?
Huh...?!
Meanwhile, the eastern forces led by Kin'emon
approach the back entrance
of the castle as planned.
My fellow warriors!
Before we proceed,
I would like to modify our plan!
It would seem that as of now,
they are still ignorant of our arrival!
So let us split our forces once more!
Half of us will infiltrate
the Skull Dome from the side,
slipping into the enemy's midst
and waiting for the moment to strike.
Meanwhile the other half will
sneak in through the back door.
There we will ambush Kaido and Orochi from both sides!
I'm on the edge of my seat!
I wonder if Momo will be there.
The samurai inch ever closer to
the castle where Orochi and Kaido reside.
Halt!
There was, however, a miscalculation.
I see.
The blueprints for the mansion were quite old.
It is no surprise there have been additions.
But it is far too conspicuous
for 2,000 soldiers to cross such a bridge!
Hey, Kin'emon...
Is... Is... Is...
Is that a pleasure hall I see over there?!
This pleasure hall is owned by
Black Maria, one of the Soaring Six.
I bet there are tons of lovely ladies in there!
Oh, Sanji!
Wait, Sir Sanji!
It's like he's being sucked in!
We're gonna sneak in, too!
We shall form a search team
for Lord Momonosuke!
You've been super worried about him!
Just admit it!
Just leave Momo's rescue to us!
That way you guys can focus on the fight!
Lady Nami! Lady Carrot! Shinobu!
You have my utmost gratitude!
In truth, it has been weighing on me!
I am counting on you!
Someone's coming out of the pleasure hall!
Is that...?
Guess he didn't find any girls...
After hearing the commotion
that Luffy and the others created,
almost all of Kaido and Orochi's
subordinates have left the pleasure hall...
Invaders!
Catch them!
Take them down!
It's Killer!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Yo! Yo!
What's taking so long?
That guy's not that strong!
Did you guys know?
Killer ate a defective SMILE fruit,
and became a Pleasure!
Hey, Killer!
If you eat this, I'll give you
a chance to save your captain!
What the hell's so funny?!
You bastards!
I'll send everyone who laughs at you to hell!
That so?
Hey, Jaggy!
Don't cause any more trouble!
So they broke out of Udon's prison...
Should we go after them?
Wouldn't hurt to get the credit...
Forget it!
It's just a few rats.
Focus on finding Yamato for me instead!
That's a much bigger deal.
Do not let Sasaki beat us to the punch!
Yes, sir!
What's the holdup?! Ice these rejects, yo!
Put 'em in a grave six feet below!
In any case...
I can't believe what Queen said...
I've been wanting...
to kill someone myself.
If the women left, the men weren't far behind.
It appears we can cross after all!
Live floor infiltration team, good luck!
– Yeah!
Nice! That's the spirit, guys!
The rest of you, follow me!
– Yeah!
Gunner and driver Usopp,
move Brachio-Tank 5 ahead slowly,
matching speed with the infantry!
Roger that, tank commander Chopper!
Proceeding nice and slow!
Keep an eye on the windows
of the pleasure hall just in case!
Leave it to me!
If you should see a silhouette…
Kin'emon!
What's all that racket outside?
Everyone, into the water!
What?!
Let's go, Brothers and Sisters!
– Yeah!
King...
I'll get even with that bastard
if it's the lickety last thing I do!
Climb all the way to the top!
But why the hell is this the only way in?!
It's absolutely absurd!
No, what's absurd is the Big Mom Pirates
allying with the Beast Pirates!
It has to be a joke!
What is Mama thinking?!
Mama's made her decision!
Forget about the alliance!
Remember the reason we actually came!
You're right!
In order to restore our reputation,
we need to find Straw Hat, kill him...
...and display his head for the world to see!
How barbaric!
More importantly...
I can become Kaido's new favorite!
Screw you, Flampe!
We made it!
Wano!
We don't know what's out there!
Prepare to fight!
Don't drop your guard!
Last time, at this very place, that damn King...
That's...!
What?! King?!
That bastard came back–
No, that's not him!
Marco?!
Hmm...
So the rumor about the Big Mom Pirates
and the Beast Pirates' alliance...
wasn't just talk.
Now...
back down you go!
Phoenix Brand!
Not on my watch!
You've got to be kidding me!
– Again?!
Why is he here?!
The next time you make it up to Wano,
you may find things are slightly different.
Huh?!
A big ship is falling meowt of the sky!
Look up there.
Haven't seen that mug...
since the war.
Marco.